Guide to the Public Art Fund Archive MSS.270
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Public Art Fund - Project Files
  - Subseries VI.B: In the Public Realm
    - Mir, Aleksandra - In the Public Realm finalist - 1 of 2, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Mir, Aleksandra - In the Public Realm finalist - 2 of 2, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Goldman, Charles, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - In the Public Realm 2000 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - In the Public Realm 2001 - 1 of 2 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - In the Public Realm 2001 - 2 of 2 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - In the Public Realm 2002 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - In the Public Realm 2003 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - In the Public Realm 2004 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - In the Public Realm 2005 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Realm Finalists -Proposals 2005, 2005-2006 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - In the Public Realm 2006 - 1 of 2 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - In the Public Realm 2006 - 2 of 2 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Sze, Sarah - "Corner Plot" - 1 of 4, 2005-2006 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Sze, Sarah - "Corner Plot" - 2 of 4, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Sze, Sarah - "Corner Plot" - 3 of 4, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Sze, Sarah - "Corner Plot" - 4 of 4, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Washburn, Phoebe - 1 of 2, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Washburn, Phoebe - 2 of 2, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Realm Application Process, 2007 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Fischer, Rob - "Tiffany Carting" - 2007 Finalist (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Shepherd, Rudy - 2007 Finalist (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Killoran, Patrick - 2007 Finalist (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Rodman, Hailey - 2007 Finalist (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Roysdon, Emily - Realm Finalist, 2007 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Sella, Marco Boggio - 2007 Finalist (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Drosdeck, Tyler - 2007 Finalist (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Benson, Frank - 2007 Finalist (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Puett, J. Morgan - 2007 Finalist (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Meromi, Ohad - "In the Public Realm" proposal 2008 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Rowe, Heather, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Simmons, Xaviera - "Bronx as Studio", 2008 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Tuggar, Fatimah - 1 of 2, October 15, 2008 - November 9, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Tuggar, Fatimah - 2 of 2, October 15, 2008 - November 9, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Xs Space, 2008 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - "In the Public Realm" - 2008 Finalists (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Realm 2008 - 2009 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Bronx Museum of Arts, 2008-2009 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Subseries VI.C: MetroTech Center
    Arranged chronologically, this series documents projects that were realized at MetroTech Center in Brooklyn, New York. Public Art Fund began organizing new exhibitions at MetroTech Center in 1993 through a partnership with MetroTech Commons Associates and MetroTech companies. These group exhibitions include work by multiple artists at the site. Materials include administrative information pertaining to each exhibition, as well as folders on each individual artist participating the project.
    - MetroTech Center - Drafts and proposals, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - MetroTech Center - Spring projects 1993 - 1 of 2, July, 1989 - January, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - MetroTech Center - Spring projects 1993 - 2 of 2, July, 1989 - January, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Devine, Dan, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Nash, Laura, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Rueckert, Stephen, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Schafer, David, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Von Rydingsvard, Ursula, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Otterness, Tom - 1 of 2, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Otterness, Tom - 2 of 2, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Chang, Jackie, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Landauer, Ken, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Martin, Walter and Muñoz, Paloma, 1996 (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Monti, John, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - "Changing Places" - General file, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - MetroTech Center 1996-1997 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - MetroTech Center 1997 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Beyond the monument, 1998-1999 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Booker, Chakaia, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Matelli, Tony, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Soares, Valeska, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Suh, Do-Ho, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - MetroTech Center 1998 - 1999 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Angus, James, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Carl, James, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Louden, Sharon, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Middlebrook, Jason, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Mosher, Kristen, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - MetroTech 1999-2000 General File (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Dodge, Jason, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Kromelow, Andrew, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Lopez, Michelle, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Rostovsky, Peter, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Tallichet, Jude, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - MetroTech Center 2000-2001 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Campbell, Beth, 2000 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Conner, Jon - "Perfect Day", 2001 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Domantay, Art, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Thomas, Austin, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Partegas, Esther, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - MetroTech Center 2001-2002 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - MetroTech Center - Publication files, 2001-2003 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - MetroTech Center FY02 - "Temporary Residents", 2002 (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Blasco, Isidro, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Craft, Liz, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Gould, Peter, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - Gould, Franco Mondini-Ruiz, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - Lehmann, Elke, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - MetroTech Center - 2002-2003 - 1 of 2 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - MetroTech Center - 2002-2003 - 2 of 2 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - City Hall / MetroTech, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - De Salvo, Roman - "Liquid Ballistic", 2003 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Fabricus, Jacob, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Gartrell, Amy - "Wishing Well", 2003 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - McKenzie, Dave, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Monkkonen, Pentti, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Tolle, Brian - "MetroSpective" - "Witch Catcher", January 29, 2003 - November 8, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - MetroTech Center 2003-2004 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Castano, Carolyn - "Nightbird", 2004 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Cohen, Jennifer - "Diamond", 2004 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Gispert, Luis, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Swanson, Mark, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - "Semiprecious" - MetroTech Center, Brooklyn, NY, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - MetroTech Center 2004-2005 - 1 of 2 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - MetroTech Center 2004-2005 - 2 of 2 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Material World - General, 2005-2006 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Material World - Budget, 2005-2006 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Material World - Peter Kreider, 2005-2006 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Material World - Mamiko Otsubo, 2005-2006 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Material World - Mathew Day Jackson, 2005-2006 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Material World - Rachel Foullon, 2005-2006 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Material World - Corin Hewitt, 2005-2006 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - MetroTech Center 2005-2006 Proposed and Realized Projects (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - MetroTech Federal year 2006 - Jackson, Krieger, Foullon, Otsubo, Hewitt (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - MetroTech Center 2006-2007 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - "The World is Round" - MetroTech 2006-2007 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Dyrenforth, Jacob - "Stand-Ins for the All-Time Greatest" - "The World is Round" - MetroTech, Brooklyn, NY, 2006-2007 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Guerrero-Maciá, Diana - "The World is Round" - MetroTech, Brooklyn, NY, 2006-2007 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Hanson, Chris and Hendrika Sonnenberg - "Soapbox" - "The World is Round" - MetroTech Center, Brooklyn, NY, 2006-2007 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Johnson, Matt - "4 Eva" - "The World is Round" - MetroTech Center, Brooklyn, NY, 2006-2007 (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - McGinness, Ryan - "Equo ne Credite, Teucri" - "World is Round" - MetroTech Center, Brooklyn, NY, 2006-2007 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - MetroTech Planning - 2006-2007 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Caesar, Jedediah - "Everyday Eden" - MetroTech Center, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Feher, Tony - MetroTech Center - "Everyday Eden", 2007 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Fischer, Rob - "As Above, So Below" - MetroTech Center, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Hayes, Paula - "Everyday Eden" - MetroTech Center, Brooklyn, NY, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Katchadourian, Nina - "Please, Please, Pleased to Meet 'Cha" - 1 of 2, November 8, 2007-September 7, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Katchadourian, Nina - "Please, Please, Pleased to Meet 'Cha" - 2 of 2, November 8, 2007-September 7, 2007 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - MetroTech 07-08, 2007-2008 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Breckenridge, Ethan - "I'm OK - You're OK" - MetroTech, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Cape, Francis, 2008-2009 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Friedman, Martha - "Waffle" - MetroTech, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Rafferty, Sara Greenberger - "Trapdoor" - MetroTech, Brooklyn, NY, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Subseries VI.D: Unrealized Projects
    - Oldenburg, Claes - Public Arts Council, 1975-1986 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Lehr, Harold - unrealized, 1978-1982 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Columbia U Site - unrealized - Public Arts Council assisted, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Christo (and Jeanne-Claude) - "The Gates" - unrealized, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Staller, Eric - unrealized - 2 projects - 1 of 2, 1981-1983 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Staller, Eric - unrealized - 2 projects - 2 of 2, 1981-1983 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Mural, W 12th St. - unrealized, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Mural, W 12th St. - unrealized, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Mach, David - unrealized, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Segal, George - unrealized, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Lovell, Whitfield, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Wong, Martin - "Mini-Pools" - unrealized, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Simonian, Judith - unrealized, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Westermann, Barbara - unrealized, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Simmons, Laurie, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Kawamata, Tadashi - unrealized - Roosevelt Island, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Meisler, Meryl - Finalist - Positive Actions: Visual AIDS, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Mendro, David - Finalist - Positive Actions: Visual AIDS, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Nils-Udo - unrealized project, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Wells, David - unrealized, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Hunt, Melinda & Lovejoy, Margot - unrealized, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Dougherty, Patrick, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Herring, Oliver - unrealized, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Ramirez-Jonas, Paul - unrealized, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Shioya, Nobi - 1 of 2, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Shioya, Nobi - 2 of 2, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Zittel, Andrea - "A-Z", 1995 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Vo, Khanh - unrealized, 1997-1998 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Bob and Roberta, 1998-2001 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Torimitsu, Momoyo - unrealized, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Frank, Andrea - unrealized, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Sone, Yutaka - unrealized - 1 of 2, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Sone, Yutaka - unrealized - 2 of 2, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Vitamvas, Gretchen & Adams, Ruth - unrealized, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Liesbeth Bik and Jos van der Pol - unrealized, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - McQueen, Steve - unrealized - "Carib's Leap", 2001 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Morris, Sarah - unrealized, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Abakanowicz, Magdalena, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Pardo, Jorge - unrealized - Madison Sq. Park Dog Walk, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Ovalle, Inigo Manglano - Seagram, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Artstart -unrealized, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Neto, Ernesto, 2006-2007 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Finch, Spencer, 2007-2008 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Huyghe, Pierre - "Life" - unrealized, 2009 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Subseries VI.E: Consulting and Other Projects
    - Arcade Outdoor Sound and Film Show, May 8, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Flushing Sculpture Proposals, 1979-1982 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - D.O.T. (Department of Transportation) Artist in Residency Program - Correspondence, 1979-1992 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Battery Park City Authority- Fine Arts Program, 1983-1995 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Williamsburg Bridge Show - 1 of 3, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Williamsburg Bridge Show - 2 of 3, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Williamsburg Bridge Show - 3 of 3, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Images from the Black Experience, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Roosevelt Island, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Columbus Park - general file and proposals - 1 of 2, 1988-1989 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Columbus Park - general file and proposals - 2 of 2, 1988-1989 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Doris C. Freedman Plaza, 1989-1993 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Doris C. Freedman Plaza, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Rothbarb, Ed - Columbus Park Artist-In-Residence program, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Schlatter, Heidi - Columbus Park Artist-In-Residence program, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Rothschild, Gail - Columbus Park Artist-In-Residence program, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Columbus Park Artist-In-Residence program - general, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Quinn, Anthony - Consulting project, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Douglas, S. Ajuba - 1 of 3, 1991-1995 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Douglas, S. Ajuba - 2 of 3, 1991-1995 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Douglas, S. Ajuba - 3 of 3, 1991-1995 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Proposals - D.O.T., 1991-1995 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Battery Park City - 1 of 2, 1993-1996 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Battery Park City - 2 of 2, 1993-1996 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Norton Gallery of Art West Palm Beach, Florida - Sculpture on the Waterfront - 1 of 2, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Norton Gallery of Art West Palm Beach, Florida - Sculpture on the Waterfront - 2 of 2, 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Public Art at Lincoln Center, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Central Park Playground at 67th St. Competition, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Phipps Houses, 1996-1998 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Downtown Kiosks, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Battery Park City - proposal, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - D.O.T. (Department of Transportation) Artists in Residency Program - General File, 1998-2004 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - "Comfort Zone: Furniture by Artists" - 1 of 3, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - "Comfort Zone: Furniture by Artists" - 2 of 3, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - "Comfort Zone: Furniture by Artists" - 3 of 3, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Orozco, Gabriel - Highline Project, 1999 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Baltimore, MAS, c.1999 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Battery Park City Authority - Sculpture, 1999-2002 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Jones, Andrew & Ginzel, Andrew - "Metronome", 1999 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Otterness, Tom - FCR - 42nd St, Hilton, 1999-2000 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Asia Society Collaboration, 1999-2001 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - FCR- Print Commission, 1999-2001 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - FCR- Hotel - General Budget, 1999-2001 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - FCR-Hotel - Sol LeWitt, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - FCR- Print Purchase, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Kauper - 42nd St - Hilton, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Press and Publicity - FCR Hotels - FY2000 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Pat Steir - Embassy Suites Hotel and Lobby, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music - LDC - 1 of 2, 2000-2001 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music - LDC - 2 of 2, 2000-2001 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Bloomberg - 1 of 2, 2000-2001 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Bloomberg - 2 of 2, 2000-2003 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Fresh Kills, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Fireman's Memorial, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - BAM Redevelopment Project - 1 of 2, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - BAM Redevelopment Project - 2 of 2, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Penn Station - consulting - 1 of 2, 2001 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Penn Station - consulting - 2 of 2, 2001 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Madison Square Park - "Target Art in the Park" - 1 of 2, 2001 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Madison Square Park - "Target Art in the Park" - 2 of 2, 2001 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Whitney - General, 2001-2003 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Whitney Biennial in Central Park - FY 02, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - World Trade Center Memorial - consulting, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - "Target Art in the Park" - FY02 - 1 of 2, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - "Target Art in the Park" - FY02 - 2 of 2, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Incubator Project - Proposal, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Queens Plaza - consulting, 2002 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Embassy Suites - Temporary Program, 2000-2003 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Holzer, Kapoor, Borofsky, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - New York Times - consulting, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Forest City - Atlantic Yards, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Whitney Biennial - 2004 Proposals (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Central Park 2004 - Biennial (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - High Line, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Langlands & Bell, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Manglano Ovalle, Inigo - Bloomberg, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Redl, Erwin - Bloomberg LP, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Finch, Spender - Bloomberg LP, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Budget Review, 2004-2006 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Jazz Lincoln Center, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Bloomberg - New Building, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Von Rydingsvard, Ursula - Bloomberg, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Benefit 2006 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Port Authority - JFK Proposal, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Armory Show 2006 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Morrison, Paul - Bloomberg LP - 1 of 2, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Morrison, Paul - Bloomberg LP - 2 of 2, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Rockefeller Center, 2006-2007 (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - Wilson, Jane & Louise - Research Material - 1 of 2, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, Jane & Louise - Research Material - 2 of 2, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Wilson, Jane & Louise - Governor's Island - 1 of 4, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Jane & Louise - Governor's Island - 2 of 4, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Jane & Louise - Governor's Island - 3 of 4, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, Jane & Louise - Governor's Island - 4 of 4, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Acconci, Vito - "Tuesday Night Talks", 1995
    - "Talks" - Federal Year 2006 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - "Talks" - Federal Year 2007 - 1 of 2 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - "Talks" - Federal Year 2007 - 2 of 2 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Armory Show, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Simmons, Gary - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Hayes, Paula - "Pond Planters" - Spring 2008 Benefit (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Downtown Brooklyn Partnership, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Water St. Consulting, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Artist proposal guidelines, undated (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Subseries VI.F: Newsstand Project
    - Newsstand Overview, undated (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Newsstand Guidelines, undated (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Newsstand - Budget/Funding, undated (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Newsstand correspondence, 1986-1993 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Designs for Newsstand / Bus Shelter- Graham, Dan / Tsien, Billie / Williams, Tod, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Newsstand Design - Blum, Andrea / Kaplan, Kenneth / Krueger, Ted, 1987-1992 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Newsstand Design - Norvell, Patsy and Halsband, Frances, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Newsstand Contracts, undated (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Newsstand Project Review, undated (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Newsstand Design Press, 1987-1994 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Newsstand Exhibition, undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Newsstand Project - Binder, undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Subseries VI.G: Doris Freedman Award, 1988; The Doris c. Freedman Award was established in 1982 by Executive Order of Mayor Edward I. Koch. "This Award shall be presented annually to an individual or organization selected by the Mayor in recognition of a contribution to the people of the City of New York that greatly enriches the public environment." Award for outstanding efforts to enrich public places in the city with works of art... The award is a tribute to the city's first Cultural Affairs Director, Doris C. Freedman. The award is presented annually on April 25th to commemorate Mrs. Freedman's birthday.
    This series includes information on recipients of The Doris C. Freedman Award, which was established in 1982 in honor of Public Art Fund Founder Doris Freedman. The award recognizes an individual or organization for a contribution to the people of the City of New York that greatly enriches the public environment. This series includes significant gaps, with no documentation included between 1995 and 2007.
    - Doris C. Freedman Award Drafts, 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 1982 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 1983 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 1984 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 1985 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 1986 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 1987 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 1988 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 1989 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 1990 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 1991 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 1992 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 1993 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 1994 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Doris C. Freedman Award 2008 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Subseries VI.H: Museum of Jewish Heritage
    - Museum of Jewish Heritage - Project Development, 2001-2003 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Museum of Jewish Heritage - Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Museum of Jewish Heritage - Contracts and Insurance, 2001-2003 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Museum of Jewish Heritage - Budget, 2001-2003 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Museum of Jewish Heritage - Finalists, 2001-2003 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Museum of Jewish Heritage - Finalists Supporting Materials - 1 of 2, 2001-2003 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Museum of Jewish Heritage - Finalists Supporting Materials - 2 of 2, 2001-2003 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Museum of Jewish Heritage - All invited artists - 1 of 2, 2001-2003 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Museum of Jewish Heritage - All invited artists - 2 of 2, 2001-2003 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Museum of Jewish Heritage - Promotional material, undated (Box 69, Folder 34)
    - Museum of Jewish Heritage - Andy Goldsworthy - 1 of 2, undated (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Museum of Jewish Heritage - Andy Goldsworthy - 2 of 2, undated (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Subseries VI.I: Fontana, Bill
    - Fontana, Bill, 1983 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Waterfront, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Fontana, Bill - "Waterways" - 1 of 2, 1991-1994 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Fontana, Bill - "Waterways" - 2 of 2, 1991-1994 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Fontana, Bill, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Fontana, Bill - Lincoln Center, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Fontana, Bill - "Waterfronts", 1992 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Fontana, Bill - "Jerusalem", 1995 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Subseries VI.J: Waterfalls
    - Eliasson, Olafur - "Waterfalls" - Drawings and proposals, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Eliasson, Olafur - "Waterfalls" - Power point presentations, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Eliasson, Olafur - "Waterfalls" - Police department photographs - 1 of 2, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Eliasson, Olafur - "Waterfalls" - Police department photographs - 2 of 2, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 14)